http://www.novatech-usa.com/privacy-cookies

Home
Privacy & Cookies
Privacy Policy This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.novatech-usa.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our web site: See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Registration Registration is optional. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). In order to register, a user must opt-in for registration during the check-out procedure or complete the online registration form. This information may be used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. Registered users can update their account profile (including shipping and billing locations, default shipping method, and payment information), view past transactions and view order status information online.Orders We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.Cookies We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. To see an more detailed view CLICK HERE.Sharing We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.Links This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Correcting and Updating Your Information To update or change registration information, to update billing and shipping information, etc., click on the Login or My Account links at the top of any www.novatech-usa.com web page to login and update your account information. You can also correct and update information by clicking the Contact Us link at the top of any www.novatech-usa.com web page and completing the online form or by calling +1 (866) 433-6682 during business hours to speak with a customer service representative.Additional Information Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or security practices should be directed to Nova-Tech International's Security Administrator by clicking the Contact Us link at the top of any www.novatech-usa.com web page and completing the online form or by calling +1 (866) 433-6682 during business hours.
